{
     "Questions": [
	     {
	      "question": "1.What are the differences between C++ and Java?",	     
	      "answer":"Form To enquiry about any courses"
	     },
              {
	      "question": "2.List the features of Java Programming language.",	    
	      "answer":"Form to give feedback regarding onging classes and etc." 
	     },
	     {
	      "question": "3.What do you understand by Java virtual machine?",   
	      "answer":"To give Feed Back about Induction and training Program"        
	     },
	     {
	      "question": "4.What is the difference between JDK, JRE, and JVM?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to update the fee details."              
	     },
             {
	      "question": "5.How many types of memory areas are allocated by JVM?",	     
	      "answer":"Form For registering in internship programs."           
	     },
	     {
	      "question": "6.What is JIT compiler?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     },   
	     {
	      "question": "7.What are the main differences between the Java platform and other platforms?",	     
	      "answer":"Form for new Registration."              
	     },
	     {
	      "question": "8.What gives Java its 'write once and run anywhere' nature?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     },
	      {
	      "question": "9.What is classloader?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     },
	      {
	      "question": "10.Is Empty .java file name a valid source file name?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     },
	      {
	      "question": "11.What if I write static public void instead of public static void?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     },
	     {
	      "question": "12.What is the default value of the local variables?",	     
	      "answer":"Form to apply leave for onging classes."
	     }
	     ]		
}
